= kisskh.ca =
[Three years ago]
[Father: Cha Sungho
Mother: Yoon Hyejin]
Cha Dohyun...
You've always been like a fool.
I need to use the restroom.
Dohyun.
Cha Dohyun.
We should go.
And we'll
come back next year.
Next year, and the year after.
No.
Let's visit every year together for life.
Cha Dohyun, you're not alone.
I'll be with you till the day I die.
Always making
foolish promises to me.
Let's go home together.
Yeo Eunho,
you've been in my life
since the day I was born,
and I'm certain you will be
for the rest of my life.
So this feeling I have for you
doesn't need to be defined.
Because no matter what,
you'll always be by my side.
Or so I thought,
until that bastard showed up.
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
If not,
can I like him?
Do you really not know,
or are you pretending?
Hey!
Back off.
He...
is mine.
Good luck then.
You guys go in first.
You know about today's
student council meeting, right?
Yeah.
I'll be there in a bit.
Okay.
[Yeo Eunho]
Please leave a message after the tone.
Have you named it?
No, not yet.
How about Cheese?
It's too common.
How about Summer?
It was born in summer.
That's too literal.
Then... Butterfly?
Cats can't fly.
You hate everything!
What do you like then?
Want a drag?
Good luck then.
You like Yeo Eunho, don't you?
If not,
[Yeo Eunho]
can I like him?
Why do you even smoke this?
What are you guys doing?
Dohyun, why are you here?
Hey.
Yeah.
Don't you remember what I said back then
when I took your key?
What key?
I remember, of course.
I think I spoke in simple enough terms
so even someone like you would understand.
Or was it still not simple enough?
Or do you think
my words mean nothing?
Seo Jaewon,
won't another demerit
get you disciplined?
Cha Dohyun.
Your second strike—
the vice principal's reaction
will be priceless,
don't you think?
Yoo Wonho,
you're a lost cause anyway.
And you, transfer student...
Hey, what the hell?
What's with that condescending tone?
You, let's talk after school.
Who the hell are you?
Why do I have to see you after school?
Did you come here acting crazy
just to lecture my friends?
Hey, wait for me.
Where do you think you're going?
Piss off!
Let go of me. What's wrong with you?
Let go of me, you bastard.
Don't move.
Asshole,
who are you to order me around?
Who do you think you are? Huh?
Well,
if you'd answered my call,
I wouldn't have seen all this.
Did you see the look in his eyes?
I thought he was going to kill someone.
So what if
he's the student council president?
Way to ruin my day.
Hey.
What was that about the key just now?
What should I do?
Spit it out.
Damn it, he told me not to tell anyone.
Cha Dohyun caught us drinking
with some girls.
You're hopeless.
No, we didn't do anything weird. Right?
Yeah.
We went home after drinking.
And then?
He confiscated the key.
Then what?
That's all? You think I believe that?
Tell me.
What was his price
for hiding your drinking?
Damn it, he told me to keep my mouth shut.
What is it?
He said whenever I hang out with you,
I have to report it to him.
What?
It's not like he asked me
to snitch on you,
but to just text him
where we are and what we're doing.
And not to bring you along
when doing bad things.
Like drinking,
smoking,
or hanging out with girls.
Eunho, I'm really sorry.
We didn't mean to betray you.
-Yeah.
-That guy threatened us!
We had no choice but to go along!
-It's true.
-Really.
What's with the ruckus?
Back to your seats!
You punks.
The bell rang a long time ago.
Everyone's present, right?
What page are we on today?
Page 86.
Page 86...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's go for tteokbokki after school.
Aren't you meeting Cha Dohyun?
It's up to me to go or not.
Is today a special day?
It's Dohyun's birthday soon.
Jihyun also happened to return to Korea.
No one beats your cooking, Auntie.
Really? I just threw it together.
It's this good even when
she just whipped it up.
If she puts in the effort,
you'll be blown away.
Oh, stop it.
How's Vietnam been?
It's been good.
Don't you dare skip meals
because of work.
Don't worry.
By the way,
why are you two so awkward?
Did you fight again?
Looks like you did.
I just know it's Eunho's fault.
It can't be
the model student Dohyun's fault.
Right?
Actually,
I did Eunho wrong today.
You did?
What did you do?
Eunho was smoking at school.
I got mad at him and his friends.
But now that I think about it,
I did go too far.
I'm sorry, Eunho.
I was just worried
seeing you smoke
and hurting your health.
Hey, Yeo Eunho.
-Hey, you punk.
-Mom! Mom!
-Mom! Mom! Ouch! It hurts.
-Are you out of your mind?
Dad, listen to me.
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Come here.
Cha Dohyun!
Damn you, Cha Dohyun!
Meet me on the roof, you jerk.
If the homeroom teacher looks for me,
tell him I went to the nurse's office.
Come on, Yeo Eunho. Stay calm.
Rip into him, cold and calculative.
Don't lose your cool;
it's just what he wants.
You bastard!
Thanks to you, I'm all bruised!
Are you seriously smiling right now?
You weren't actually
sorry yesterday, were you?
You disloyal traitor.
You were in the wrong to begin with.
I just took a drag out of curiosity.
Bring it on, you prick.
Who told you to smoke?
Come on!
Damn it, let me go.
I figured if I hung around you
long enough,
you'd eventually be mine.
What the hell? Am I an object?
What? The cigs...
Do you smoke?
But now it feels like
you're slipping through my fingers.
Why did you even get on my case
about smoking then?
If you were curious,
you could've just told me.
Open up.
Suck it.
Suck it hard, Eunho.
Cha Dohyun, you...
You've been acting strange.
Does he think he's my only friend?
[Cha Dohyun]
[Block Contact]
[Blocked]
What are you doing?
Hey, Yihyun.
Let's go for lunch.
The guys are going to the snack shop.
Lunch?
Sure.
So, did you duke it out with Cha Dohyun?
The nerve of him to lecture me
when he's a chain smoker.
Weird.
Right? Isn't it weird?
He freaked out
about me smoking yesterday,
but today he made me...
Never mind. Forget it.
He's not right in the head.
Eunho.
Just believe what you see.
Get off me! Damn it.
It's so freaking hot.
With today's heat,
whose idea was it to buy
instant noodles with broth?
Bet it was you.
Damn you.
Where's your brain?
Hey.
You still haven't made up with him?
Jeez. For crying out loud.
Him and his death stare.
I can't stand this.
Just say sorry and get it over with.
What did I do wrong?
Why should I apologize?
Yeo Eunho, just apologize!
You guys eat.
Are you okay?
Don't touch him.
Bear with it.
You're overreacting.
Don't get too close to
those delinquents.
Then I won't get on your case anymore.
Or just hang out with Kwon Yihyun...
No, hang out with me.
Wherever you want to go—
internet cafes, pool halls—
I'll go with you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Why must I only hang out with you?
Crazy. Don't you have any friends?
Yeah.
You're the only one
I have.
[Summertime]
Yeo Eunho.
What?
Wanna come home with me?
People might get the wrong idea.
Did you get the wrong idea too?
Make a wish.
I hope I never fight with Yeo Eunho,
and we stay happy forever.
I told you
you're the only one I have.
Don't you have something to say to me?
Do I?
I don't want to be alone today.
Stay still. It's my birthday today.